Dragon Quest XI is the ninth Dragon Quest game.
I was kinda excited.
Then I see this shit
and I immediately uninstalled and refunded the game.
I never get offended by video games.
If it's edgy for the sake of being edgy,
that doesn't cut me.
If it has derogatory stereotypes,
it's just an artistic choice!
Honestly, if I download a game from Steam, and the intro says,
I'd be like, "Eh, if the soundtrack's good..."
But when I see a POTATO in a Medieval game, it makes my fucking blood boil
Europeans first encounter potatoes in Peru, way after the Middle Ages,
yet these "game publishers" keep forcing potatoes into our Medieval fantasies.
Us gamers are tired of company bigwigs pushing us gamers around
*RISE UP*
Us gamers.
Wouldn't surprise me if in the future, you can only unlock other vegetables through lootboxes.
And, yes, even EA fell for this.
Fortunately, they hate single player, so never again.
Even Kingdom Accurate MacHistoricAccurate has...
...no potatoes...
But then some cheeky fucker modded them into the game...
It was me!
I have to show these giant game corporations
that they can never make games moddable.
Publishers, what I'm saying is that, if your game has potatoes,
but no mountainous rainforest climate,
your game is bad and should be illegal.
And even if you have that climate,
where are the llamas?
They come from the exact same place,
and some scientists believe they are the same species.
Including them is not an option.
It's a requirement.
Wait...
Did Dragon Quest fulfill these requirements?
Shite, I refunded too soon.
Ah, now I have to play through this 100-hour long game
with one overworld theme.
*overworld theme plays
This is pure torture. Why does my job include playing video games?
Dragon Quest XI has like every country ever.
So there is a chance there is an Incan country.
But no country has their correct food,
like Japanland has potatoes, Arabicland has potatoes,
Veniceland? No pasta, just potatoes.
But Hawaiiland has lobsters!
But real gamers will notice it's the wrong species.
And in the Netherlandsland...
Soon™.
Unlike in real life, they don't seem to eat any tulips.
I never checked the Frenchschoolland,
because French people usually don't care about food.
But, there is a Chinese mountain village where everyone has Australian or South African accents.
And they eat corn.
The remaining countries are Ancientgreekland and Norwayland.
Norwegians.
A people that live exclusively on butter and salmon
has neither of those things.
By this point, I think the wrong foods are intentional.
I think the games industry just made this game to mess with me.
The final country is Spainland, and it's probably only in the game so they can say
"Oh, the Spanish brought potatoes to Europe, so everything is fine."
*music swells*
It's not fine.
I am outraged.
Those are all the countries! There have been no Incas and no llamas!
Dragon Quest gets a one out of seventy thousand-
I found the llama.
Not what I expected.
Should have been more specific.
But, well played, Square.
Uuugh, I think this means I have to travel the world again.
ONE OVERWORLD THEME
CHANGE THE FUCKING SONG
That's the entire world again.
And I haven't found the correct climate.
So, in my humble opinion,
Dragon Quest is too bad to get a grade.
The best way to describe it is unplayable!
Dragon quest is a complete gameomatic failure
Dragon quest didnt just die it was mur-
Wait, is this a mountainous rainforest?
So, yeah, it gets a seven out of ten. Pretty solid.
But needs more music varieties.
And has some other big flaws.
*outro music*
BUT WAS THAT THE KILIAN EXPERIENCE LAWLOLOLOLAWL EXDEEEEE